I know it's hot today,
but let's work hard!
Where's everyone else?
Did they catch cold?
It's a boycott.
Boycott?
Miyabi and the others,
until their conditions are met,
they said they won't come
to your class, Onitchi.
Conditions?
They want a different
homeroom teacher.
What?
This is the first time since
this academy started.
These problems after problems,
they interfere with those
of us running things properly.
To have class end so suddenly,
if the parents find out about this,
it'll be terrible, Director!
Aizawa Miyabi's mother is
a commentator on a talk show.
If she talks about this on TV,
what's going to happen?
Onizuka-sensei,
this concerns you, so you must
have something good planed.
- No, not really.
- What's that?
Those who don't want to come
to my class shouldn't come.
Talking like that again!
Don't you have anything
intelligent to say?
Well then, Onizuka-sensei,
we'll need you to take
responsibility.
Please consider this and levy
appropriate punishment!
Okay then, here's what
we'll do.
Fortunately it's almost
summer vacation.
So, Onizuka-sensei,
by the time fall session starts,
you must persuade all,
and I mean all,
of your students to return.
Otherwise you will be
immediately fired.
That's too lenient, Director!
In return for that, there will be
one more punishment
- for Onizuka-sensei.
- What's that?
A reduction in salary.
So, your salary for this month
and next month will be cut in half.
Wait! Hold on!
Then what about my bonus?
You wouldn't have any yet!
You've only been at this school
a month!
Please, take some pity on me!
Oh my, look at the time!
Excuse me, I have to prepare
a summary for the company...
Everyone, listen...
Even if Onizuka convinces you,
you better not go back.
You know what will happen
to anyone who betrays us.
Hey, Dizzy, are you listening?
But you know,
I want to go to class.
If you talk to Onizuka,
you'll be banished!
Okay, I got it.
Dare no tanjôbi mada
oboeteru?
You got it?
"When I think about you,
I can't sleep at night."
"I can't hold it in any longer."
"Teacher, I want you
to see all of me."
"Teacher, I want to give you
everything."
"I'll be waiting for you
after school today
in the health room.
Your Tomoko."
That's perfect!
You're pretty good at writing
something so naughty, Erika.
Maybe you're actually
doing it with someone?
How rude!
Here, give this to Onizuka.
But I'm not in love with
Onizuka-sensei.
I know that!
We're going to use this
to get Onizuka to come out
and come onto you.
Then we'll catch him.
You got that, Dizzy?
Don't be so dizzy!
That's why everyone
calls you "Dizzy"!
- I'm sorry.
- You'll do it, right?
Because we're best
friends, right?
Yeah.
Damn. There isn't any
good work.
Hey, how about a running
a house by the sea?
Sounds good, if we do that,
all the chicks'll come!
I think you'd better take
a look in the mirror.
Shut up, stupid!
Hey Kikuchi, isn't there
something in your PC?
Of course not, there's no
easy jobs that pay 50,000.
Stop saying that and look harder!
So Onitchi, why do you
need money so badly?
It's almost summer and I bought
all kinds of stuff.
The suit, shoes, slacks,
sunglasses...
I don't get any bonus,
and my salary's been cut.
I figured it was something
like that.
Guess I'll have to find
some work...
Teacher, here!
Top prize, 1,000,000.
- I think this is too hard for me.
- Not that, here!
500,000 for referral...
- Hey, Nanako, how about you?
- What? No way!
C'mon! You're the cutest
girl in our school!
- Stop it!
- I'm serious.
- You think so?
- Yes, for sure!
That's right...
try singing something.
Okay, here goes.
Can you celebrate?
Can you kiss me tonight?
- We will love long long time
- Oh well.
Hey, Tomoko!
Whaccha doing?
I know, you want to come
to my class, right?
C'mon, say something!
I'll get scolded if I talk to you.
- Huh?
- I'm sorry!
I'm sorry!
SORIMACHI TAKASHI
MATSUSHIMA NANAKO
KONDÔ YOSHIMASA
ENJÔJI AYA
NUMATA BAKU
KOBAYASHI MASAHIRO
IDA KUNIHIKO
KIRARI
IKEUCHI HIROYUKI
YAMAZAKI YÛTA
TOKUYAMA HIDENORI
KUBOZUKA YÔSUKE
NAKAMURA AIMI
KURODA MIKI
OGURI SHUN
FUJIKI NAOHITO
MABUCHI ERIKA
TATEISHI RYÔKO
DAVID ITÔ
NAKAO AKIRA
SHIRAKAWA YUMI
English Subtitles by
STUDIO NEW MEDIA
Subtitles Edited and Timed by
SCHWEFELHEXAFLUORID
D-ADDICTS
www.d-addicts.com
Directed by
NAKAJIMA SATORU
A Production of
KANSAI TEREBI & AVEC
Man! What a pain!
- Hard, isn't it?
- Yes it is.
Oh, how about this girl?
- No, I don't think so.
- Really?
She's kind and a good girl,
I think if you talk to her
she'll understand.
No matter how nice she is,
I don't think this face
and style will work.
What? Aren't you looking
for students you
can convince to come
back to class?
No. You see, I'm looking
for girls in my class
that might become idols.
Idols?
Yeah. See, they give 500,000
for referrals!
How about her, or maybe her?
Oh man, if Nanako wasn't
so tone deaf...
Just what are you thinking?
If you don't get all your
students back by fall session,
you'll be fired you know!
Right now, that 500,000
is more important.
Just when I thought you were
taking things seriously!
Those of you who get bonuses
don't understand
what I'm going through.
I don't know what the heck
you're talking about!
I saw you, Fuyutsuki-sensei!
Why didn't you tell us?
- What?
- Playing innocent again, here!
When did you start doing this?
What? I don't know anything...
No need to be bashful!
You look the most beautiful
in this one!
Who took these?
It doesn't look like
a pro cameraman.
- The original is much better.
- But I...
How shocking! Just what are
these youngsters thinking of!
Getting so worked up,
it's shameful for a teacher!
I really don't remember this!
I've been meaning to tell you this
from before, Fuyutsuki-sensei.
Aren't you being a little
too flashy?
What do you mean by flashy?
Even if it summer, don't you
think you're showing
a bit too much skin?
You're a teacher, you should
dress more like a teacher!
Or are you trying to get your
student's attention?
Kotani-sensei, you're being
too harsh!
You always get so defensive
when it comes
- to Fuyutsuki-sensei.
- Who's the one getting defensive?
- Please!
- You always...
I'll call the publisher!
Sir, Head Teacher!
What do you think of this?
I think a plain face won't work...
- What do you mean plain?
- That means a face like yours.
Sir!
Oh yes, you could be in an ad
for a word processor!
Oh, yes, yes!
What do you think sir,
Fuyutsuki-sensei could be
a model for next year's
spring pamphlet!
Okay, it's Onizuka
so it should be easy.
But if he doesn't do anything,
then you'll have to make
the move.
- What? How?
- For crying out loud!
Show him your panties
or get him to touch your breasts.
You can't even figure
that out? Stupid!
- But I'm kinda scared.
- He's coming!
If you mess this up,
we won't forgive you!
Okay.
- Where's he going?
- Someone's coming!
Thank you for the letter.
Tomoko-kun...
You see...
I've always thought of you...
Thought of you as a good girl.
It's after being separated
I began to see...
I'm also a man.
You see, ever day has been
lonely for me.
Tomoko-kun, what are
you doing?
This is our secret...
Just what's the meaning of this?
What?
- What do you mean?
- Don't play dumb!
Selling a person's picture
to a magazine.
- Oh no, you found out?
- Of course!
Well you know, it's not fair
to keep your beauty to yourself.
What a smooth talker.
So did you get your reward?
Oh, I was going to give
it to you tomorrow.
Why are you always
so irresponsible?
Hey, I'll treat you to dinner
tonight, how 'bout it?
There you go again!
You know, that money's
rightfully mine!
I'm sorry!
I don't believe you got
Onizuka's and Nakamaru's
- mailboxes mixed up!
- Unbelievable!
- You are so dizzy!
- I'm sorry!
You drive me nuts!
I don't know why I've stuck
with you for so long!
I'm sorry Miyabi-chan!
- I'll get it right next time!
- Don't ever talk to me again!
Miyabi-chan!
You're banished!
- I'm home!
- Welcome home!
- Just in time, can you help us?
- Okay!
Take care of the customers,
okay?
Yes.
- Oh!
- Hey!
Tomoko, why're you here?
- This your place?
- Oh, welcome...
What are you doing, stupid!
I'm so sorry, this girl...
- It's okay.
- Bow and apologize!
- I'm sorry, teacher.
- Teacher?
Are you Tomoko's teachers?
I'm her homeroom teacher,
Onizuka Eikichi.
I'm her English teacher,
Fuyutsuki.
You should have said
something sooner!
Mom! Bring them a beer!
- Please don't worry!
- Sorry, thanks!
- So is this a home visit?
- Oh, yes!
Teacher, isn't this girl so dizzy?
Is she giving you trouble?
- Not at all!
- No need to be nice.
It doesn't bother us.
What are you saying,
that's how you feel!
We have a son in intermediate
school,
everyone asks him, is your sister
really related to you?
She's an ugly duckling.
There's Aizawa Miyabi-chan
from her class, right?
She's the only one who
takes care of her.
We always tell her,
be more like Miyabi-chan.
She's going to end up being
a housewife anyway.
- Please.
- Thank you.
Wow! This is great! It's so cute!
It's just like you!
All these stuffed animals!
It must have taken forever
to collect all these!
Is something wrong?
I've left her speechless.
It's a picture of you
with Aizawa Miyabi-san!
We've been best friends
since elementary school.
Teacher, look at these too!
This is our graduation from
intermediate school.
And this is when we went
to Disneyland together.
Miyabi-chan is really great.
She's smart and pretty,
she's always done well in school.
And she's good at sports too.
You are not in a brassier shop!
Uh, that's not...
I'm just checking
on these high school girls
nowadays...
That's right, Tomoko, you must
have lots of clothes in here!
- See!
- Look at these!
You've got a lot of mature
clothes!
It all matches with Miyabi-chan!
It all matches with
Aizawa Miyabi-san?
Yup!
Because I want to be like
Miyabi-chan.
She's got so much that I don't.
But that's over now.
I think she hates me now.
You should have more
confidence in yourself.
That's impossible for me.
I'm not smart and I'm no
good at sports.
Even my little brother
calls me "Dizzy".
So, do you have a dream?
Something you want to be
in the future?
It's like my dad says, all I can
become is a housewife.
So... I'd like to get married
by the time I'm 20.
That's pretty popular now.
Like Amuro-chan, or Hinagata.
Is that really okay?
It's okay.
There isn't anything else
I can do.
That's not true!
It may be true that Aizawa-san
has a lot of things you don't,
but I'm sure you have a lot that
Aizawa doesn't too!
Don't you think so, Onizuka...
What's that?
Can't you think of anything
else besides money?
I'm sorry.
Maybe this is a little too plain.
- How about this?
- Will you butt out?
- This one then?
- Stop it already!
Geeze, I'm going home already!
I don't have time for this.
You have to stay,
you're her sponsor!
What's that?
I'll have you pay with your
payment from that magazine.
Hey! I took care of dinner!
I know you accepted the meal for
free from Nomura-san's parents.
- Why don't you try this on?
- It's alright! I feel bad!
Don't worry about it!
Because it's a present
from Onizuka-sensei!
Tomoko, if you don't like it,
then there's no need to get it.
Okay, here you go!
Fuyutsuki-sensei,
why are you doing this?
I know how she feels.
A long time ago, I suffered
from a serious complex.
No way!
All the kids around me
looked so much better.
I copied how they dressed
and talked.
I lost confidence in myself.
That's when my homeroom teacher
in intermediate told me.
You should be you.
After that, I stopped comparing
myself to others.
And then miraculously,
I began to like myself.
The most important thing
for a woman,
I think it's to be able to have
confidence in yourself.
Waiting for a prince in
shining armor to come -
that's no way for Nomura-san
to spend her life.
What?
It sounds like your talking
to yourself.
What are you saying?
I'm just saying that as a woman.
You should be you.
Don't go using lines from
other's memories!
Does it look strange?
Not at all! It looks great!
Right?
Oh, yes! It looks great!
Just like an idol!
Are you thinking of something
again?
No, what are you...
Don't you think this is a little
too flashy?
Not at all!
It looks great on you!
I think something breezy
like this is better!
It's summer after all.
Well, that's what I was thinking.
It's okay, it's summer, isn't it?
Then I'll take this,
I can use my bonus.
Oh yes, a swimsuit too...
Kotani-sensei, shopping?
You like some pretty
sexy clothes, don't you?
Well... this... I'm thinking
of buying it for a relative.
I would never wear
something like this!
Oh my!
My, my, my!
Nomura-san, what are you
doing here?
- Um, I...
- Come with me.
You've been skipping
my class lately.
I'm sorry.
I've promised your parents
I would make you
into a fine woman.
That's not right, do it over.
That's great, your sewing is nice.
Oh my! Well done,
Aizawa-san!
Thanks to your instruction,
teacher!
You're always excellent
at whatever you do.
- Thank you very much!
- Isn't this color off?
- This is crooked!
- Ow!
- It hurts!
- What is this?
Who said that you could make
something like this?
This is a valuable class for your
future prospects as a wife.
Look at Dizzy!
And look at this sewing.
Just how old do you
think you are?
I'm sorry.
Why is everything I do no good?
Cheer up, Tomo-chan.
But you know,
Miyabi-chan hates me,
and Kotani-sensei
gets mad at me.
Tomoko, what are you
doing here?
Teacher, what are you
Well, I'm looking to see if
I can find a good girl.
What's this?
Hey, it's pretty cute!
What's it's name?
- I'm Gâko!
- Gâko?
I'm Onizuka Eikichi,
pleased to meet you.
- Hello, Onizuka-sensei.
- Hello.
But you know,
is that really a duck?
It looks more like a ghost.
How rude! Tomo-chan worked
very hard to make me, you know!
Oh, I see.
Are you Tomoko's good friend?
- Yup! Of course!
- You know I've noticed...
Your friends don't seem
very happy lately.
They're angry. They've saying
it would have been better
if she hadn't been born.
Right, Tomo-chan?
Yeah...
Cheer up!
Okay!
So teacher, what can we
do to cheer up Tomo-chan?
Tell us, tell us, teacher! Teacher!
Tomoko...
You've been mislead before...
What?
So would you give
me your future?
- Want something to drink?
- Oh, please.
Now then!
Teacher...
Um... I...
I've never done it before.
What's that?
- Hey, Onizuka!
- Where've you guys been?
It's been a long time!
Why'd you call us so suddenly,
we're busy you know!
- Is this the girl?
- She's not very sexy.
What are you saying!
Those old guys like this better!
I see! Just hurry up!
A Lolicon, huh? Onizuka,
didn't know you were into that.
Well, I think it'll sell.
How about this? More flashy
make-up would be better,
- don't you think?
- It's only for...
So then, how about
more like this?
What do you think?
Oh my! How nasty!
Will you cut that out!
Okay then!
Shall we go with this?
But I don't think I'm ready
to do this.
What are you talking about?
But, aren't you making an AV
or some kind of dirty video?
Will you set her straight? I think
this girl's got the wrong idea!
Quite a misunderstanding.
Tomoko, you're going
to be an idol!
What?
You're going to enter
an audition!
- I'm sure you can make it!
- What?
Change.
Wow! Tomoko!
- This is perfect!
- You think so?
Hey, why're you getting
in the picture?
Well, it's been years since
I've seen anyone like this!
You're too cute!
You're blinding! You're radiant.
It's blinding!
He's just saying stuff
he doesn't even mean.
He's just trying to blind that girl!
You sure we should
be doing this?
You know, it's a mistake
for him to be a teacher.
Tomoko,
leave the thinking up to me!
What is this? You want to
be excused from class?
Um... I... want to enter
an audition.
Audition?!
Just what are you thinking?
This is your doing.
- She's doing this on her own.
- I wonder...
Don't be like that,
please help her out.
Me? Why?
Well, because she decided
to do this after wearing
the clothes you picked
out for her.
So... is this okay? After she finally
got up the confidence. Oh well...
Well?
- This is for your own good.
- Kotani-sensei...
Yes?
Couldn't you give her a chance?
What? You too?
Well, I think this is the first
time she's ever voiced
a desire to do something
for herself.
Do you seriously think this
girl can become an idol?
I just want to support
her desire...
Well I'm opposed
to miss contests
and those types of events!
That's your personal opinion
Kotani-sensei,
I don't you should inflict it
upon the students.
What's that?
My! You're quite
enthusiastic today.
What are you saying!
- Kotani-sensei...
- What?
I think we should let
Nomura-kun go.
I'm opposed. Fuyutsuki-sensei,
are you aware
of the rule forbidding
outside activities?
Isn't that right, Head Teacher?
What? Really?
Nakamaru-sensei?
Nakamaru-kun!
Y-Yes?
- Are you listening?
- I'm sorry!
It's written in chapter 7,
section 25-2!
Nomura-kun, see.
You see, as a member
of this academy,
we can't have you enter
this audition.
Besides, being an idol
is good for nothing.
When you get older,
no one will care about you.
A woman's happiness
is to marry a nice man
and make a family, Nomura-san.
Hold on! Will everyone stop!
Fuyutsuki-sensei, are you
feeling okay today?
I want her to decide on
her future for herself!
Fuyutsuki-sensei,
we are protecting
the school regulations.
Rules are rules.
I don't think you should be
too tied up in all that...
- Did you say something?
- Oh, I'm sorry.
Teacher, it's alright.
Nomura-san...
I'll give it up.
You better come to class!
Damn it! And we were so close!
- Hey Saejima, light!
- Come on!
Trying to deceive a high
school girl is terrible.
Tomoko. She shouldn't have told
that Kotani and just entered!
Don't talk to me 'bout that!
Man, you're a sore loser!
Oh well, how about if I give
you my peeping videos.
Those toilet video's I confiscated...
They're pretty popular.
If you copy these, I'm sure you
can make a pile off them.
Say Miss, would you give me
your future?
- Forget it!
- What?
You're missing out!
- Hey, Miss.
- What do you want!
Why don't you give me
your future.
I'm home!
What happened to you?
Today, I met a wonderful man!
So wild, and sexy!
He's the total oppose of Dad!
What?
Did you do something?
- Stop it!
- Yoshiko!
We're you accosted by
some strange man?
Don't be silly. It was a moment
of electricity!
Like Matsuda Seiko!
- Really? Is he a dentist?
- I won't stand for it!
Those kind of men,
they're all punks from some
third rate college.
I'll introduce you to a fine
man from our school.
His name's Teshigawara-sensei.
He's an elite from Tôdai!
Stop it!
The one thing I will
never marry is a teacher!
That's right. Teachers bring
home all their stress
from school and unload
it at home.
And then during summer
vacation they just stay at home.
Mama, you suffered a lot
marrying Dad, didn't you?
I don't want you to suffer
like I did.
I'll be okay.
You again!
I'm doing this for your good!
So why can't you do like
I tell you?
- I'm sorry.
- It's not "sorry", right?
Hey! Stop playing
in the hallways!
Hey! Idiot!
Didn't I tell you not to
play in the hallway?
- Yes, I'm sorry!
- My flower arrangement!
Oh, those kids!
Tomoko, did you make this?
It's great!
- But I have to fix it.
- But it looks great!
I know, let's do this!
Stop it! What do you think you're
doing in this important lesson!
- Hey, how about this?
- I think this is better.
Hey, you're great!
That's perfect!
Onizuka-sensei! I will not
forgive your behavior!
I'll report this to the head
teacher
and have you compensate
me for damages!
Witch!
Oh, Tomoko...
Head Teacher,
please come with me!
Okay! Please don't pull me!
THE NEW FACE AUDITION
Wow, this is so many people!
Sorry Miyabi for coming so
suddenly to this audition.
- Erika, you're always like that.
- She's always so slow.
We're all here to cheer you on!
Miyabi's sure to win!
- Why don't you audition?
- What?
It'll be okay, you can fool them
into thinking you're
in high school.
- No, she can't.
- What are you talking about?
The girl we know isn't here!
I figured from the beginning
that girl was no good.
What, please...
Hey!
- Sorry 'bout that!
- You're late!
Onizuka-san!
Oh! Fuyutsuki-sensei,
you're here too?
What about Nomura-san?
Thank you for waiting,
the star is here!
Okay! Let's go!
Hey, isn't that Dizzy?
No way! Her image's not
any different.
- Was she always that cute?
- Thank you very much.
Will she be alright?
She'll be fine!
Now then, thanks for coming!
Miyabi! Miyabi! Miyabi!
I'm Number 17, Aizawa Miyabi,
17 years old.
- That Miyabi's really into it!
- Damn.
She saw Tomoko's entered
- and is even more determined!
- Thank you very much!
Now then, next please!
Tomoko! It's Tomoko!
Tomoko!
- Tomoko! Tomoko!
- Next is...
Tomoko!
N-Number 18...
I'm... No... No... No...
You're Nomura Tomoko-san,
right?
Yes, that's right.
Thank you very much!
Is she going to alright, Onitchi?
- Yes, she'll be fine!
- Really?
Okay! Thank you very much!
Next is...
- Massaka sama ni ochite desire
- Man she's good!
That's because she's always
at karaoke!
Honô no yôni moete desire
Koi wa dance, dance, dance,
dance hodo
Muchû ni narenai nantene
Sabishii
Get up, get up, get up,
get up, burning heart
Massaka sama ni ochite desire
Honô no yôni moete desire
- Koi mo dance, dance, dance...
- I can't bear to watch!
This is too much for Tomoko!
Are you doubting Onitchi?
She'll be fine!
A miracle will occur, right?
Onizuka-sensei?
Get up, get up, get up,
get up, burning heart
- So, Miyabi.
- What?
Could you say I referred you?
No way! Never!
What's that attitude toward
your teacher!
- Ow! Fuyutsuki-sensei!
- Onizuka-sensei!
Now, finally, it's time for
speech presentations.
First is entry number 1,
Makino Yûko-san.
Please!
Listen, do you seriously think
you can become an idol?
You're not going to make
it anyway,
you should leave before you
embarrass yourself.
But, everyone's cheering me on.
I'm saying this for your
own good.
Don't you hate public speaking?
Has anything I ever told you
been wrong?
You understand?
What's this?
Please, Nomura Tomoko
sends you her regards.
Please!
Please give her your
consideration!
Number 17, Aizawa Miyabi.
Please!
Number 17, I am Aizawa Miyabi.
Teacher,
would it be okay if I go home?
What? You've come this far!
I can't do this.
And Miyabi-chan told me I should
leave before I embarrass myself.
If you do that, are you sure
you won't regret it?
You should give it your
best until the end.
The most important thing
in this life to me...
is my friends!
Next is number 18,
Nomura Tomoko-san.
Please!
Um, well...
No... No...
Nomura Tomoko-san, right?
Oh, yes it is...
Take your time.
Um, well...
I am...
Nomura Tomoko.
Yes, we know that already.
Oh no, this is it.
And we came this far.
I wonder where
Onizuka-sensei is?
Yo! How're you, Gâko!
Who are you?
Me? I'm a student too.
- Hello!
Hey! Something's bothering
your good friend.
That's right. It looks like she
doesn't know what to talk about.
This is about you Tomoko.
It doesn't matter what.
Come on out and just
say whatever!
Teacher! There isn't a single
thing I can be proud of!
Tomoko, that's what I love
about you, your sincerity!
Teacher, what should I do?
Do whatever you want!
You should be you!
You're not an ugly duckling,
you're a swan!
Do you understand?
Tomoko! If you understand,
then answer me!
You understand, don't you,
Tomoko!
Gâko...
You know, there's someone
I'm really grateful to right now.
Really? Who?
You see,
I was really happy,
the first time Miyabi-chan
talked to me.
Miyabi-chan's your best friend?
In elementary school,
even though I didn't have
a single friend, she said,
let's walk home together.
Miyabi-chan,
I'll never forget that moment.
After that...
Miyabi-chan always
protected me.
Even though she was the most
popular girl in class,
she still played with me,
the most clumsy one in class.
To me...
To me, Miyabi-chan
was my hero.
I would always think,
I want to be like Miyabi-chan.
But...
I'm going to stop that now,
Gâko.
I have to learn to like
myself more.
If I don't...
If I don't, then no one
else will like me.
No one else will become
my friend.
I will do my best!
I'll do my best,
from now, my awkward
silly self...
I'll learn to like myself more!
That's what I've decided!
Wow, I was surprised!
I never dreamed you would
win the speech award!
Well, you've got talent!
You were really cool!
Thanks!
Miyabi-chan!
This is a present for you,
teacher.
Are you sure?
For me!
Thank you!
What, no referral fee for
winning special awards?
Good morning!
So it's finally summer vacation!
- Teacher!
- Good morning!
You were great yesterday!
Oh, no I wasn't...
I'll have to try hard like you,
Nomura-san!
What?
Get it right here!
Special, one of a kind!
We've got it all here!
You better get 'em now
while you can!
Please, excuse me!
Looks who's here!
I'll take one of these,
and one of these!
- Thanks, come again!
- Okay!
Oh, by the way, Onizuka-sensei,
you haven't forgotten about
your class, have you?
Of course not!
I'll take care of it when
the time comes.
Hey! You! No pushing!
No pushing!
That Onizuka...
That Onizuka!
30,000...
40,000, 50,000!
Hey! You scared me!
Looks like you've made
quite a bit.
Thanks to you. I consider it
like a referral payment.
- My share.
- What?
It was thanks to me that
Nomura-san had
a change of heart.
You're frightening.
Okay, since it's summer vacation,
I'll treat you to something.
Hey! You can't fool me!
What are you trying!
I've been waiting patiently,
it's summer vacation, isn't it?
Fuyutsuki-sensei...
2016-04